Abhishek Jadhav

Portfolio url: https://captainaj1.github.io/portfolio/

Mobile: +91 8623947396 Email: <u>aj9145348@gmail.com</u> Country of Citizenship: India

DOB: 08/12/1995

CAREEER SUMMARY

I have been working as a Web Developer and Video Editor for the past one year. Well versed with Php with working experience in developing web applications in core php, Drupal & WordPress CMS. Also, I have produced a number of videos for YouTube channels and Artists on a professional level.

Currently working as a Real Estate Video Editor & Graphics Designer. Aiming to obtain a creative and challenging position as a Non-Linear Video Editor.

CORE COMPETENCIES

- Videography, Video Editing, colour correction & colour grading
- Photography, Graphic Designing
- Developing Web applications in Php, Drupal & WordPress CMS
- Adept in software installations & updates
- YouTube SEO

WORK EXPERIENCE

Real Estate Video Editor & Graphics Designer – October 2019 to Present

SaudaGhar- Pune, Maharashtra

- Editing Property footage, adding essential graphics and color grading techniques as needed. Editing various property Vlogs, Explainer videos and promo videos.
- Producing creative videos & graphic designs for social media, banner images for website.
- Keeping the company website up to date with embedding latest video uploads.
- Handling companies' social media accounts and managing YouTube channel SEO.

Video Editor – June 2018 to Present

Pune, Maharashtra

- Scheduling video shoots on different locations, arranging camera setup and equipment's.
- Directing and recording videos for different outdoor and indoor setups individually as well as within a team.
- Editing music videos, trailers, Ads, promos, learning videos for different Artists, YouTube channels and social media.
- Managing the YouTube SEO for a couple of channels.

Web Developer – May 2018 to May 2019

NSoft Technologies Pvt. Ltd- Pune, Maharashtra

- Developing static and dynamic web applications in Drupal and WordPress CMS.
- Writing code in core Php.
- File handling and Database management.
- Front-end customization in HTML/CSS.

EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATIONS

Bachelors in Computer Engineering (2017)

Pune University -Pune, India

SKILLS AND SOFTWARE PROFICIENCY

- Videography, Video Editing, Color correction and Color grading
- Audio Mixing & Synchronization
- Photography, Graphic Designing
- Adobe Premiere Pro, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe After Effects, CorelDraw
- Camera Operation: Sony A7S, Nikon D5200/D5300, Cannon 5D
- Adept in software Installations & updates
- Developing static and dynamic web applications
- Php, JavaScript, jQuery, MySQL, Drupal, WordPress
- Social media handling, YouTube SEO

COURSES AND CERTIFICATION

- ✓ Advanced PHP training at Lavenir Institute of Professional Studies (LIPSINDIA), Pune
- ✓ Programming in Java at NIIT, Pune

EXTRA CURRICULAR

- Trained Musician, proficient in all skin instruments primarily Tabla. Professionally Performing live with Individuals and bands.
- Certification in Tabla from Akhil Bhartiya Gandharva Mahavidyalay, Pune.
- Actively involved in sports, Field Hockey player for School and College.